4life.com 2014-06-03

# Privacy Policy

                      T O G E T H E R , B U I L D I N G P EOPLE ®
Privacy Policy
By entering this site, you consent to the use of your personal information as set forth below.
You can read our Privacy Policy below to see what information we collect and our security assurance.
This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information that is collected by 4Life Research, LLC, and
each of 4Life’s subsidiary companies, when you are on a 4Life website, and when you use 4Life services.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that 4Life does not own or control or to people that 4Life does not
employ or manage.
4Life uses information for five general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for
certain products and services, to contact you about specials and new products, to maintain and manage the distributor genealogy,
and to allow other distributors to manage their businesses.
Information Sharing. 4Life uses the information we collect solely for our business purposes. We do not sell or share personal
information to third parties other than those third parties who provide services vital to our business (see Third-Party Providers,
below) and to other distributors (see Other Distributors, below). However, we may also provide aggregate information and
statistics about our customers, sales and related site information to our third-party providers, but this information and statistics
will include no personally identifying information. Please note that we may release information in good faith as is reasonably
necessary to comply with the law or protect our rights.
Cookies and Sessions. Cookies are essential “invisible” data files that act as an electronic messenger between your computer
and our website. Internet browsers have a notification option to let you know when an “invisible” cookie is being sent to you.
Through your browser options you can choose not to accept the cookie. However, in not accepting the cookie, you may not
be able to experience all functions of 4Life.com.
Sessions are encrypted and enable us to temporarily save personal information about you on our server. The most basic
session information includes data about what is in your shopping basket. Each time you login, a new session is created pulling
your information from 4Life’s database. This saves you time, as you will not have to re-input your Personal Information each
time you visit or shop with us. 4Life uses sessions, rather than cookies, as an enhanced security measure.
We may use your IP address to identify and verify secure logins, help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our
websites. Your IP address also may be used to gather broad demographic information and to recognize customer traffic patterns
and site usage. This information aids us in merchandising and in developing the design and layout of the site.
Information Collection and Usage. 4Life may collect information from several different points on our website. This information
includes but is not limited to the length of each visit, how often you visit, which areas of our site you visit, and items that you
purchase, and is collected solely for the purpose of making your 4Life experience the best it can be. This data helps us make
better choices about the information we include on our site. We also collect and store personal information necessary to process
orders you place and to maintain your status as an independent distributor. This includes your name, mailing or physical address,
email address, telephone number(s), credit card information, distributor identification number, order history and bonus history.
We also allow distributors the opportunity to post their photo and personal story on their replicated website if they wish.
  4Life Research U S A , L L C    9 8 5 0 S . 3 0 0 W. S a n d y, U T 8 4 0 7 0 P: 801.562.3600 F: 801.562.3611       w w w.4 life.co m

                      T O G E T H E R , B U I L D I N G P EOPLE ®
In addition, we may also use the information collected to occasionally notify you about important changes to our website,
new services and offers that we feel might interest you. If you would rather not receive this information, simply follow the
directions in the mailing to unsubscribe from the mailing list. You can also unsubscribe in the Account Management
section of 4Life’s back-office.
Third-Party Providers. 4Life uses the services of third-party providers for certain services. In order for these third-party
providers to perform their functions, we must provide certain of your personal information to them. These third-party providers
include merchant processing, delivery service providers and our software providers.
Other Distributors. As a network marketing company, 4Life provides certain information to distributors regarding the other
distributors and customers in a distributor’s line of sponsorship. If you enroll as a distributor with 4Life, your name, rank, email
address, address, telephone number and Life Points purchased will be provided to other distributors in your upline and/or
downline. No other personally identifiable information will be shared with other distributors.
Security. Whether you place an order or create a profile, we use industry-standard secure server software (SSL) that encrypts
all information you input before it is sent to the server. In addition, all of the customer data collected is protected against
unauthorized access. Credit card numbers are encrypted and stored in our server for six months after orders are entered.
No data transmission over the Internet will be 100% secure. While we take steps to protect your personal information, we cannot
guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Upon receiving your transmission,
we make all reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. However, you are ultimately responsible for maintaining
the secrecy of your username, passwords and/or any account information.
To check the security of your connection, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If
you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active. You can also double-check by looking
at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from “http”
to “https.”
Some versions of browsers and some firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers like the ones we use to
process orders. In that case, you’ll be unable to connect to the server, which means you won’t be able to mistakenly place an
order through an unsecured connection. If you cannot access the secure server for any reason, please print our order form
and place your order by phone or by fax.
Surveys and Contests. Our site may request information from you via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or
contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information
requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip
code and age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for
purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site and for our internal marketing research purposes.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance. Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions
to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information
to outside parties without your consent.
   4Life Research U S A , L L C   9 8 5 0 S . 3 0 0 W. S a n d y, U T 8 4 0 7 0 P: 801.562.3600 F: 801.562.3611      w w w.4 life.co m

                       T O G E T H E R , B U I L D I N G P EOPLE ®
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance. We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens
Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products
and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years of age or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only. This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not
to information collected offline.
Links. Our Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other
sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every web
site that collects personally identifiable information from them. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by
this website.
Your Consent. By using our website, you agree to let us collect and use information per the terms of this privacy policy. If
we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information
we collect and how we use it.
Making Changes to Your Personally-Identifiable Information. You may update your personal information as necessary by
logging into the Account Management section of 4Life’s back-office. Within 4Life’s back-office, you have access to your account
information and have the ability to edit your information. In addition, you may contact us at distributorservices@4Life.com to
update your profile.
Contact Us. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, contact distributorservices@4Life.com.
This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 6, 2010.
   4Life Research U S A , L L C    9 8 5 0 S . 3 0 0 W. S a n d y, U T 8 4 0 7 0 P: 801.562.3600 F: 801.562.3611   w w w.4 life.co m
